junction.co.za 2015-07-17

# 

**Privacy Policy**

  1. Introduction 
  2. Information Collection & Use 
  3. CareerSeeker Registration 
  4. Recruiter Registration 
  5. Resume 
  6. Cookies 
  7. Log Files 
  8. Sharing 
  9. Legal Disclaimer 
  10. Links 
  11. Communications 
  12. Security and Data Storage 
  13. Access and Choice 
  14. Social Media Widgets 
  15. Choice/Opt Out 
  16. Blog Disclosure 
  17. Notification Of Changes 
  18. Contact Us 

[](https://privacy.truste.com/privacy-seal/CareerJunction-\(Pty\)-Ltd/validation?rid=060598a9-0591-413d-9b1e-94435d72ff9c "TRUSTeonlineprivacycertification")

This privacy policy applies to [http://www.careerjunction.co.za](http://www.careerjunction.co.za/) owned and operated by Interactive Junction Holdings (Pty) Ltd. ("CareerJunction"). This privacy policy describes how Interactive Junction Holdings (Pty) Ltd. collects and use the personal information you provide on our web site: [http://www.careerjunction.co.za](http://www.careerjunction.co.za/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

Interactive Junction Holdings (Pty) Ltd. has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable by the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this web site, [ www.careerjunction.co.za](http://www.careerjunction.co.za/) and does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile website. 

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at [ https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

**1\. Introduction** ** **

The Company(s) referred to herein as "CareerJunction" refers to Interactive Junction Holdings and any of its divisions, including but not limited to [www.careerjunction.co.za](http://www.careerjunction.co.za/)

**2\. Information Collection & Use ** ** **

CareerJunction is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. CareerJunction collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

**3\. CareerSeeker Registration** ** **

In order to use the functionality of this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give the following information: 

  * Full Name 
  * Phone Number 
  * Email Address 
  * City or Town & Country (Province) 
  * Username 
  * Password 
  * Communications(Yes/No) 

This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. 

**4\. Recruiter Registration** ** **

Information that is collected from subscribing Recruiters will be used to contact the Recruiter about the services for which they have expressed interest. If Recruiters want to change their information their company supervisor has access to do this using the Supervisor Tools functionality. 

  * Company Name 
  * Phone Number 
  * Facsimile Number 
  * Email Address 
  * Website Address 
  * City or Town & Country (Province) 
  * Communications(Yes/No) 

**5\. Resume** ** **

We request the following information from a CareerSeeker in our resume form: 

Personal Details, including: 

  * Full Name 
  * Date Of Birth 
  * ID Number (Optional) 
  * Affirmative Action CareerSeeker (African/Coloured/Indian/Disabled/Female) 
  * Phone Number 
  * Additional Phone Number (optional) 
  * Email Address 
  * Location 
  * Languages 
  * Education Details 
  * Employment History 
  * Skills 
  * Associations 
  * Achievements 
  * My Next Job 
  * Availability 
  * Searchability 

This information is used for the Online Recruitment process and this includes sending CareerSeeker resumes to a Recruiter for the purpose of a CareerSeekers job application process where such resume data may then be stored by the Recruiter for future recruitment consideration. A Recruiter may also make contact with a CareerSeeker for recruitment opportunities as a result of a resume search conducted by the Recruiter on searchable resumes on the CareerJunction database. If we have trouble processing a request, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. CareerJunction does not store this information. CareerJunction stores email addresses for sole purpose of sending this one-time email (and tracking the success of our referral program). 

Your friend may contact us at [info@careerjunction.co.za](mailto:info@careerjunction.co.za) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

CareerSeekers who have been placed in a job through the CareerJunction Network are eligible for an online voucher that can be redeemed at [www.exclus1ves.co.za](http://www.exclus1ves.co.za/). The information we require for these purposes are employment details, recruiter details and personal details. The information will be stored for verification purposes only and will be treated as confidential. If a CareerSeeker gives us permission we may publish details of their placement. 

**6\. Cookies** ** **

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by CareerJunction and our partners, affiliates, analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for tracking usage behaviour, recognise repeat users, manage users access and track user settings. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

**7\. Log Files** ** **

As is true most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. 

**8\. Sharing** ** **

We sometimes share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to personally identifiable information. 

We also partner with third parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names or other information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. We will not voluntarily disclose any information about individual users to third parties, except as described in this privacy statement, or to comply with applicable laws or valid legal process, or to protect the rights or property of CareerJunction and its partner sites. 

CareerJunction maintains relationships with outside service providers for some of the services offered through our site, for example MyGate and Virtual Card Services (VCS). 

The information these providers make available may be presented in a "framed" format, where the CareerJunction border will surround the pages served by the service provider, or where pages have the look and feel of CareerJunction. In either case, the service provider is prominently identified. Please be aware that any information you provide on those framed pages is provided directly to those service providers and is subject to their security and privacy policies. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these outside service providers because their privacy practices may differ from ours. 

**9\. Legal Disclaimer** ** **

We may also disclose your personal information: 

  * as required by law, such as to comply with subpoena, or similar legal process 
  * when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to government request, 
  * if CareerJunction is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so 

**10\. Links** ** **

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that CareerJunction is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected on pages of this site. 

**11\. Communications** ** **

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify their username and password. Users also have the choice to subscribe to our newsletter. A user can unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time from both our site and the newsletter itself. 

CareerJunction may use your information to contact you about promotions and services. You are entitled, at any stage, to opt out of this service, by clicking on the "opt out" option on the email correspondence. This will redirect you to the My Portfolio page where you will be able to unsubscribe from newsletters, promotional communications and/ or service announcements. 

From time to time we may send out critical service announcements. Users are not able to unsubscribe from critical service announcements, which contain important information about the service. 

**12\. Security and Data Storage** ** **

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information online. When asked to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number), the information is encrypted and is protected via secure sockets layer (SSL) encryption technology. 

We also do everything in our power to protect user information offline. Access to all of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our Client Service Manager) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure, access controlled environment. If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as their email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal details provided to us. This can be done from the user's My Portfolio page or by emailing our Client Service Manager at [ info@careerjunction.co.za ](mailto:info@careerjunction.co.za) . 

**13\. Access and Choice** ** **

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, ask to have it removed from a public forum, directory or testimonial on our site or deactivate it by making the changes on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [ info@careerjunction.co.za ](mailto:info@careerjunction.co.za) or by contacting us by telephone or postaal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**14\. Social Media Widgets** ** **

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you visiting on our site, and may set cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**15\. Choice/Opt Out** ** **

Users who no longer wish to allow their resume to be searchable by our subscribers may opt out of this facility by going to their My Portfolio page, to My Resume and select to be non-searchable. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt out of receiving it by going to their My Portfolio page, to My Newsletter and select to not receive newsletters. 

**16\. Blog Disclosure** ** **

The Blog functionality on CareerJunction functions as a Social business network built around professional and user generated career content. This includes articles, ideas, questions, answers, links and comments. Users are able to customise content by topic and location, watch specific content, follow specific authors, comment on posts and create their own posts. The purpose is to create a discussion forum around careers. If you choose to submit information or comments to the blog on the site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by the other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in the forums. 

**17\. Notification of Changes** ** **

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage prior to the change becoming effective. 

**18\. Contact Us** ** **

**Phone Us**   
+27 21 818 8600 

**Fax us**   
+27 21 818 8609 

**Email us**   

**Visit us**   
2 Fir Road   
Black River Park   
Third Floor   
Central Building   
Observatory   
7925   
South Africa (Western Cape) 

**Snailmail Us**   
PO Box 87   
Century City   
7446 

Effective Date: 23 March 2015
